http://www.panterandhall.com/pages/privacy-policy

social-twitter
PRIVACY POLICYPRIVACY NOTICEWe take our responsibilities as a data controller seriously and are committed to using personal data we hold in accordance with the law.YOUR PRIVACYWe are committed to maintaining the trust and confidence of those who express interest in our activities. We do not sell, rent or trade our mailing lists with other companies and businesses for marketing purposes.COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL DATAPersonal information means any information that may be used to identify you, such as, your name, title, telephone number, email address or mailing address.We collect personal information and use that information to:- send you e-mailings which will keep you updated on the current activities of Panter & Hall Ltd, such as private views in the gallery and invitations to art fairs- contact you if we need to obtain or provide additional information- check our records are rightUNSUBSCRIBINGYou can unsubscribe to general mailings at any time by contacting us by email on enquiries@panterandhall.com or by post at Panter & Hall, 11-12 Pall Mall, London, SW1Y 5LU.ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONYou are entitled to access, amend or delete the personal information we hold on you. Please email your request to enquiries@panterandhall.com or by post to Panter & Hall, 11-12 Pall Mall, London, SW1Y 5LU.CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY NOTICEWe may change our Privacy Policy from time to time and without notice. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will publish it on our website.
payment-american_express
payment-apple_pay
payment-bitcoin
payment-dankort
payment-diners_club
payment-discover
payment-dwolla
payment-forbrugsforeningen
